[
{"question": "Completa la palabra: D_I__RO", "response": "DINERO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: HOM_R_", "response": "HOMBRE" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: FA_S_", "response": "FALSO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: CH__O", "response": "CHICO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: A_TO", "response": "AUTO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: M_T_", "response": "MOTO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: V_D__O", "response": "VIDRIO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: B_A_O", "response": "ARROZ" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: D_M__GO", "response": "DOMINGO" },
{"question": "Completa la palabra: D_R_I_", "response": "DORMIR" }




]
